onthesnow.com 2017-09-30

# Snow Report | Snow Totals | Cams | OnTheSnow

Mountain News Corporation is strongly committed to protecting your privacy and providing a safe online experience for all of our users and subscribers while offering the highest quality publications and services to them. Because we gather certain types of information about and from users so that we can fulfill your requests and better serve your needs, we feel you should fully understand the terms and conditions surrounding the collection and use of this information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather, how we use it, how to correct or change it, and what steps we take to safeguard personal information provided to us online. We urge you to read the complete Online Privacy Policy below, as well as our Terms and Conditions of Use, and contact us if you have any questions, but offer this short summary to highlight key points.

We collect personal and non-personal information from you to provide information and service, to understand your interests, and to conduct our business.

We may share personal and non-personal information about you with third parties in the circumstances described in this policy.

We use cookies, web beacons and other technologies to provide personalized content, certain functionalities, and to better understand the features our visitors prefer.

We reserve the right to share information to satisfy a legal request, protect people or property, or in connection with a transfer of one or more of our business units.

What Information Do We Collect About You?  
Personal Information  
Information Collected Automatically  
What Do We Do with Information We Collect?  
How Do We Share Personal Information?  
Advertisers, Sponsors and Promotional and Business Partners  
Important Note  
How Do We Use Cookies?  
How Do We Use Web Beacons?  
What About Third Party Advertisers?  
How Can You Control Your Personal Information?  
Security of Your Personal Information  
Links  
Changes in Corporate Structure  
Visitors Outside the United States  
Changes to Our Privacy Policy  
Contact Information 

* * *

**WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU?**  
You can visit our websites, read articles and other materials, and check on offerings without giving us any personally identifiable information. So that we can provide our users and subscribers with the most efficient and enhanced, personalized service, we request information about you in certain circumstances, and collect certain information automatically.

**Personal Information**  
We collect personally identifiable information, such as names, mailing addresses, and/or e-mail addresses, when you register at one of our web sites. Website visitors may register to receive one of our e-mail updates, respond to a survey, or enter online contests and sweepstakes. Registration may be required to participate in message boards, bulletin boards, or chat rooms at our websites or to take advantage of special offers. Sometimes registration can be accomplished by submitting only a user name and password. Other types of offerings require submission of additional information. The information we collect may include your e-mail address, name, address, phone number, age, gender, hobbies, family information, and similar demographic information or information related to your interests. Some of our sites may offer you the opportunity to receive offers directly from third parties. Registration forms will indicate what information is required and what information (if any) is optional.

**Information Collected Automatically**  
Our websites automatically collect certain information, such as your IP address, browser type, domain name, access times and referring website address. This helps facilitate your online experience at our websites. In addition, we use cookies to track usage patterns at our site and to control the display of ads, as well as to offer other functionalities (such as screening for age, and "recognizing" you to speed up your log-in when you visit our sites). See below for more detail on cookies.

**WHAT DO WE DO WITH COLLECTED INFORMATION?**  
We use information you provide to fulfill your requests, improve our products and services, and operate our business. For example, we use personal information so that we may display or send custom, personalized content to our website visitors and to send newsletters, e-mails, promotional material, surveys and other updates, information or offers to our users and subscribers. A user may, at any time, opt out of receiving promotional offers by e-mail.

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a way to unsubscribe. Please see the “Choice and Opt-out” section.

We may produce reports for advertisers, sponsors and vendors containing anonymous, aggregate information about our users and subscribers, such as demographic, age and online usage information. This allows us to provide content and offers that are most relevant to our subscribers and users and to work more closely with advertisers.

**HOW DO WE SHARE PERSONAL INFORMATION?**  
Personal information is available to Mountain News Corporation, including its brands and affiliates, and its or their technical and fulfillment agents and consultants who make this site and our publications, products and services available to you.

Mountain News Corporation and Its Agents. Mountain News Corporation may access both anonymous, aggregate demographic data and any personal information you provide for internal marketing or other business purposes, services or products we offer likely to be of interest. Web host firms, technical and database consultants, advertising agencies, and fulfillment firms, including firms assisting us in offering contests and promotions, may have access to personally identifiable information in the course of making our products and services available. All companies working for Mountain News Corporation must comply with our information collection, use and disclosure policies, and are not permitted to sell your information to third parties or to use it except as authorized by us and you, or as permitted or required by law.

**Advertisers, Sponsors and Promotional and Business Partners.**  
We share anonymous, aggregate demographic information (such as gender, age, income, hobbies, interests, etc.), and anonymous information obtained from cookies and similar technologies, with our advertisers, sponsors, promotional and business partners, and with participating vendors at sites offering online sales opportunities. No personally identifiable information is disclosed to any of these third parties in providing these reports.

We may extend e-mail offers to you on behalf of our business partners about their products or services, but only if you have indicated that you would like to receive such offers. Although Mountain News Corporation may receive a fee from our business partners for this service, Mountain News Corporation sends those offers on behalf of the business partner, and does not share your e-mail address with them. Of course, you may opt out of receiving those offers at any time.

At our websites, visitors will also have opportunities to sign up directly with certain advertisers and sponsors to enter contests or sweepstakes, receive e-mail updates, or to receive information directly from them. Third party vendors and advertisers will also use technical and other consultants. We urge visitors to carefully review the privacy policies of these firms. Mountain News Corporation is not responsible for the privacy policies and procedures of any third party.

**Public Postings.**  
You should be aware that if you voluntarily disclose information, personal or otherwise, online in any community area (whether through Mountain News Corporation's websites or any other service available online), that information can be collected and used by others. For example, if you use chat, forums, bulletin boards or message boards, or if you post personal information online (such as your e-mail address, photograph, etc.), you may receive unsolicited messages from others. Mountain News Corporation has no control over this use of your personal information.

**Important Note**  
We reserve the right to use or disclose any information without notice or consent as needed to satisfy any law, regulation or legal request; to conduct investigations of consumer complaints or possible breaches of law; to protect the integrity of our site and our property and assure adherence to our terms of use; to protect the safety of our visitors or others; to fulfill your requests; or to cooperate in any legal investigation or process.

**CHOICE/OPT-out**  
If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication.

**HOW DO WE USE COOKIES?**  
Your Web browser offers so-called "cookies" which, if you allow their use, store small amounts of data on your computer when you visit a website. Cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information about you and therefore cannot be used to identify you personally. Cookies assist us in tracking which of our features you like best. Cookies also enable us to customize our content according to your preferences. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying your browser and our websites are viewable even if you disable the cookie function on your browser. However, if you disable cookies, some advanced and customized features or offerings will not be available to you. Our third party advertisers may also use cookies.

**Cookies we use:**

**CrazyEgg**

  * [](https://www.crazyegg.com/cookies/)[](https://www.crazyegg.com/cookies/)<https://www.crazyegg.com/cookies/> \- Cookies **  
**
  * [](https://www.crazyegg.com/opt-out/)[](https://www.crazyegg.com/opt-out/)<https://www.crazyegg.com/opt-out/> \- Opt Out

**icevedmnc**

  * to identify our users across devices session

  * to serve the end users their recently viewed resorts

**DFP (ad-server)**  
GoogleAdServingTest

  * To serve ads on the page

**Google Analytics**  
_utma

  * keeps track of the number of times a visitor has been to the site pertaining to the cookie, when their first visit was, and when their last visit occurred.

_utmb

  * takes a timestamp of the exact moment in time when a visitor enters a site

_utmc

  * takes a timestamp of the exact moment in time when a visitor leaves a site.

_utmz

  * keeps track of where the visitor came from, what search engine you used, what link you clicked on, what keyword you used, and where they were in the world when you accessed a website.

_gadz

  * used by Google for a variety of purposes (eg, ensuring Frequency Caps work correctly) which include Adsense if you have Adsense enabled.

_utmt

  * Session cookie from Google Analytics. Used to throttle request rate.

**New Relic**

NREUM

  * Used for page load timing. This session cookie is only created in browsers that do not support the Navigation Timing API. When a browser supports the Navigation Timing API, a native interface can be used to determine navigation start time.

**HOW DO WE USE WEB BEACONS?**  
Some of our Web pages may contain electronic images known as Web beacons, which are also called single-pixel gifs. These images allow us to count users who have visited those pages and to deliver co-branded services. We also may include Web beacons in promotional e-mail messages or newsletters in order to count how many messages have been opened and acted upon. Web beacons are not used to access your personally identifiable information but they are a technique we use to compile aggregated statistics about our website usage. Web beacons collect only a limited set of information including a cookie number, time and date of a page view, and a description of the page on which the Web beacon resides. Some of our Web pages may also contain Web beacons placed there by our advertising partners to help us determine the effectiveness of our advertising campaigns.

**WHAT ABOUT THIRD PARTY ADVERTISERS?**  
Some of the banner ads displayed in our websites are provided by outside companies. These ads contain cookies and may also contain Web beacons. Unlike cookies and Web beacons used by Mountain News Corporation in content it controls at its Web sites, cookies or Web beacons received with banner ads are collected by our advertisers and we do not have access to this information. We use reputable third parties to serve some or all of the advertisements that are placed within our sites and they may use information (not including personally identifiable information) about your visits to our sites and other sites to assist in serving advertisements to you. They may share anonymous information with their clients such as date/time of the banner ad shown, the specific ad shown, the IP address, etc. Google/DoubleClick DFP is our third party ad server. If you would like to know more about their information gathering practices and "opt-out" procedures, please see [](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/)[](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/)<http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/>

**HOW CAN YOU CONTROL YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?**  
We believe that choice in how and when you are contacted is key to customer satisfaction, so we offer several ways for you to update your contact information or change your preferences.

**1.**  If you have an online account at one of our websites, you may be able to log on and update or change your contact or account information. Check the site for further information.

**2.**  You may unsubscribe to any of our online e-mail updates by following the unsubscribe instructions in the body of any message.

**3.**  To Opt-out of of Google Interest Based Ads please see [](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/)[](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/)<http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/>

**4.**  You may write to us and update your contact information or ask that we not share your personal contact information with third parties at:

Mountain News Corporation,   
c/o Privacy Coordinator,   
PO Box 17895,   
Boulder, CO 80308.

In those instances, we will retain your information in a "do not promote" file in our database. MNC - Feedback_OTS

**5.**  You may also contact us at [Feedback_OTS@mountainnews.com](mailto:Feedback_OTS@mountainnews.com).

We will take commercially reasonable steps to implement your opt-out requests promptly, but you may still receive promotional information from us by mail for up to 60 days due to printing and mailing schedules, and up to 10 days for e-mail.

**SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION  **  
Your personal information may also be protected by the password you created when you registered at one of our websites where this feature is offered. The confidentiality of any password is yours to protect. You may change it anytime by following the instructions at the website where you registered.

Although we use our best efforts to assure that your data remains secure when maintained by us, security during Internet transmissions or within any system cannot be assured. Mountain News Corporation employees are made aware of its privacy practices through periodic communications and training. We limit access to personal data only to those Mountain News Corporation employees or agents with a specific need to access or retrieve this information. We store data on multiple service systems, in controlled, secure environments. To maintain the highest level of security, we conduct internal reviews of our security measures on a regular basis. Remember, however, that any personal information you post in chat rooms or message boards is available to anyone. We ask our agents, promotional and business partners, and trusted fulfillment partners to provide assurances of reasonable security, but are not responsible for the privacy or security practices of any third party.

**LINKS**  
Mountain News Corporation may offer links to or from Web sites it controls to other sites within the Mountain News Corporation family as well as to sites operated by third parties. We offer links to third party sites so that you can conveniently visit our vendors and advertisers or locate other content likely to be of interest. We are not responsible for the content, practices or policies of sites operated by third parties and urge you to inquire about them before providing any personally-identifiable information.

**CHANGES IN CORPORATE STRUCTURE**    
In developing our business, we might sell certain assets, or the company, or parts of it, may be sold, merged or otherwise transferred. In such transactions, user information, whether personally identifiable or otherwise, may be one of the transferred assets.

**VISITORS AND SUBSCRIBERS OUTSIDE THE UNITED STATES  **  
Our websites and the servers that make these sites available worldwide are located in the United States. All matters relating to these sites are governed by the laws of the State of California in the United States. Any information you provide in registering at one of our web sites will be transferred to the United States. By visiting our sites and submitting information, you authorize this transfer, processing and use.

**CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY**  
We will occasionally update this Privacy Policy as necessary to protect our users and to comply with a changing environment. We recommend that you check the policy when you visit our site to be sure you are aware of and understand our current policy. If we make material changes to this policy or in how we will use or collect your personally identifiable information, we will prominently post such changes prior to implementing the change. We will not make material changes in how we handle previously collected personal information that have retroactive effect unless legally required to do so, and we will e-mail registered website visitors information on material changes to this policy. Your continued use of the Site means you accept the updated privacy policy.

**CONTACT INFORMATION**  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices, please e-mail us at [Feedback_OTS@mountainnews.com](mailto:Feedback_OTS@mountainnews.com).

Please include the URL of the Web site . Requests under California Law SB 27 should be directed to [Feedback_OTS@mountainnews.com](mailto:Feedback_OTS@mountainnews.com) and include the information noted in Your California Privacy Rights.

Or you can contact us by mail at:

Privacy Coordinator  
Mountain News Corporation  
PO Box 17895,   
Boulder, CO 80308.

Updated May 5, 2017
